Rafael López Martínez

UX Designer

Profile

After a few years studying and working in programming, I decided to make a change in professional future and focus on something that always have interested me: Videogame design, economy design and specially UX design.

Contact

+34 630 20 27 31

Sant Fost de Campsentelles, N°7 Spain

lopez.rafa@hotmail.com

https://rengrow.github.io/Portfolio/

Skills

- Proficient in Adobe Creative Suite
- Experience working in teams with Agile and version control tools
- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills
- Ability to work independently and in collaborative team
- Time management and project management skills

Lenguages

Spanish - Native

Catalan - Native

English - Advanced

Education

2013 - 2015 IES Carles Vallbona

Vocational training / education in networks and microcomputer systems

2016 - 2018 IES Carles Vallbona

Higher Degree of Multiplatform Application Development with honors

2018 - 2019 Centre de la Imatge i la Tecnologia Multimèdia | CITM (UPC)

Unfinished Bachelor's degree in Video Game Design and Development

2021 - 2024 Universitat Oberta de Catalunya

Bachelor's degree in Digital and Multimedia Interaction Techniques

Work Experience

2017/06 - 2017/11 SETDEVELOPERS SL.

Junior Programmer

Developing a mobile app using Xamarin and C#, using IOC principles and administrating a database using MySQL.

2018/06 - 2019/09 SETDEVELOPERS SL.

Junior Programmer

Developing a mobile app using Xamarin and C#, using IOC principles and administrating a database using MySQL.

2019/09 - 2022/09 SCM Logística y trazabilidad SL.

Mid-level Programmer

Developing apps using: C#, JavaScript, Vue and integrating 3rd Party APIs in an Agile environment.

Administrate databases in SQL Server for numerous customers and being in contact with them to talk about new implementations that they could need.

2023/06 - 2020/07 Larian Studios

PlayTester

Playing Baldur's Gate 3 before it releases. Giving feedback about the encounters in the game, the interaction with the characters and my experience with the game.